restaurant facade
entryway
ambience
dress code
coat check
greet
maître d’
waiting list
party size
booth request
high chair
follow
place setting
placemat
centerpiece
condiment
wine list
compare
entrée
appetizer
dietary restriction
doneness
ingredient
select
course
portion
side dish
seasoning
server station
assist
itemized check
service charge
gratuity
payment terminal
split payment
settle up
coat rack
exit sign
leftovers
to-go box
farewell
depart
banquette
wine cellar
open kitchen
salad bar
dessert station
service pass
dish return
warming station
host podium
private dining room
alfresco area
kitchen hatch
prix fixe
house salad
roasted chicken
steak
seafood platter
vegetarian dish
gluten-free dish
spicy sauce
gravy
mashed potatoes
risotto
sorbet
walk-in
fully booked
under my name
no onions
less spicy
on the side
share a dish
box it up
separate checks
corkage fee
minimum spend
compliments to the chef